Aubrey Oyoolo

Computer Science Student.

I am a tech enthusiast. I like to solve problems and research on efficient algorithms and data structures. I am currently interested in gaining experience in the tech field. I am learning as much as I can as a Computer Science major and working on small projects.

Baton Ruge, USA

github.com/oyoolo

(225) 508 2667

linkedin.com/in/aubrey-oyoolo-073614199

EDUCATION

Business Information Technology.

Jommo Kenyatta University.

08/2016 - 08/2017

Nairobi, Kenya

Courses

Financial Accunting.

 Fundamentals of Computer Systems.

 Computer Operating Systems.

Introduction to Business.

Communication Skills.

• Introduction to Computer Organisation.

• Fundamentals Of Computer Systems. Mathematics For Business.

Computer Science Baccalaurette

Louisiana State University.

08/2019 - Present

Courses

3.55 Major GPA, 3.2 Cum. GPA

 Computer Science I and II using Java.

 Advanced Data Structures and Algorithm Analysis.

 Object-Oriented **Programming**

• Calculus I and II.

Discrete Structures.

· Ethics In Computing.

Engineering Statistics.

ACHIEVEMENTS

Dean's List Spring 2020. (01/2020 - 05/2020)

Awarded to students who completed at-least 15 college-level hours with a semester grade point average of 3.50 to 3.99.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Intern.

Safaricom.

05/2017 - 08/2017 Nairobi, Kenya Safaricom is the leading telecommunications company in East Africa.

Achievements/Tasks

 Learned and introduced to back-end development using PHP and .NET.

- Debug HTML/CSS code.
- Introduced to QA and Testing.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Java (Intermediate)

Android Studio(Beginner), Springboot(Beginner), Eclipse, IntelliJ.

JavaScript

Vanilla Javascript (Intermediate), React, and React-Native(Beginner), Node JS (Beginner).

HTML/CSS

Bootstrap, Various Libaries.

JSON

JSON file and data manipulation.

XML

XML data manipulation.

Version Contol and Dependencies

Using Git, GitHub, Gradle, Maven and Ant.

SOFT SKILLS



INTERESTS



CERTIFICATES

CPR Cerification (06/2019 - Present)

Completed the cognitive and skills evaluations following the curriculum of the AHAH® First Aid CPR AED Program.

PERSONAL PROJECTS

On GitHub. (03/2016 - Present)

• A collection of academic and personal coding projects.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Security Ambassador. Penn National Gaming.

08/2018 - Present

Baton Rouge, LA.

Has ownership interests in 39 gaming and racing facilities, and video gaming terminal operations across the U.S.

Tasks

- Respond to medical emergencies and complete Illness/Injury reports.
- Demonstrate outstanding internal and external service following the "Red Carpet Service" program guidelines.
- Prepare Security reports on time and ensure accurateness and completeness.
- Maintain First Aid/AED certification.
- Ensure no patron under the age of 21 boards casino
- Assist the Maintenance department in an emergency condition.

Contact: Travis Dabney - 225-224-4250.

REFERENCES

Nictor Angaya, Colleague. *Contact: 225-933-8327*

Jumah Lumbasi, Friend.

Contact: 225-281-6254